Guide to the Daniel S. Greenberg papers, [ca. 1961-2010]
Greenberg, Daniel S. papers,
- Series II: Newspaper and Journal Clippings
  - Subseries Ia
    - National Labs, 1983-1994 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Nuclear weapons, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Nursing, 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Opinion and survey research, 1996-2004 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Obesity, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Nature and science, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Osteopathy, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - PCAST, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Patents, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Physics, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Pauling, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Peace institute, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Post Office, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Pot holes, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Prabhakar, Arati (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Press Criticism, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - President Campaign, 1974-1988 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Prizes, 1982-1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Professional deregulation, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Public opinion, 1978-1988 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Preventive medicine, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Price, Derek, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Priore, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Progressive, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Proxmire, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Psi res, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Psych surgery, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Radiation, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Rasmussen report, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Reagan and science, 1980-1988 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Research and development statistics, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Red Tape, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Reports, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Restrictions on research, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Ridicule, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - SALT, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Safety issues, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - SBIR, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Seveso, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Schmitt, Roland, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Science writing, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Science publications, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Science and society, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Schweiker, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Aharks, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Solar, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Schmitt, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Slaughter, John, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - SST, 1970-2002 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Stockman, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Sununu, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Tenure, 1978-1986 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Three Mile Island, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Waxman, Henry, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - University Enroll, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Whistle blowing, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - White House Science Council, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Wolfe, Sid, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Women in science, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Yellow Rain, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Crisis in science, 1986-1996 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Crisis in science, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 1A)
  - Subseries Ib
    - AAUP, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - AAHRPP, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - AAMC, 2002-2005 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - AAAS next wave, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - AMA, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - ACAD, 2001-2005 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Agriculture patent, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Alternative contract methods, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Angell and Relman, 2000-2005 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Animals in research, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Anti-science skepticism, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Arizona, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Australia, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - AUTM, 2002-2005 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - AZT, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Bayh-Dole text, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 16-17)
    - Biotechnology Industry, 2001-2005 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Berkeley, UC, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Blockbuster deals, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Blumenthal, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Books and articles to CET, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Botox, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Budget cuts, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Breastfeeding, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Bureaucracy- HIPPA, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - CSPI, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Canada, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - CME, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - California, University of, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Clinical trials, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Clips quoted, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Cochrane collaboration and center, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Coca-cola- dentistry, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Codes of conduct, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Cohen-Boyer, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Columbia University, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Commercialization- effects on university, 2001-2003 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Consumer research, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Conflict of interest, 1987-2003 (Box 14, Folder 40-41)
    - Conflicts, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Conflict resolution organizations, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Cornell, 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Cost effectiveness, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Credit disputes, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - CRS, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Culture of science, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - D-Code, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Data sharing, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Deaths in research, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Deceptive practices, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Defense research, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Detail reps, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Developing countries research exploitation, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Direct to consumer, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Disclosure, 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Drugs- deceptive promo risperidone, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Duke, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Entrepreneurship, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Environment, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Ethics, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Europe, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Evidence based medicine, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Exploit research populations, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - FDA, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Federal policy, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Fines for whistle blowers, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Florida state, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Florida, University of, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Florida tech and South Florida, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Food, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Foreign experience, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Foundations, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - France, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Fraud, Misconduct, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Gene banks, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Genentech, 2003-2006 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Gene therapy, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Golden Rice, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Google, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Grant seeking, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Harvard, 2001-2004 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Hopkins, 2002-2005 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Hughes, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Human genome, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Human research, 2002-2005 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Hype-research, 1998-2003 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - ImClone, 2001-2004 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Industrial pollution, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Industry, 2002-2005 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Industry research and development, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Informed consent, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Innovation, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Insider training, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - IRB, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Intellectual property, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Interview notes and texts, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Irresponsible institutions, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Jobs, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Journals competition, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Kaufmann fund, 2004-2006 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Korn, Dave, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Koski, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Lobbying, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Love of research, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Madey, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Marketing to children, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Material transfer agreements, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Medical education industry, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Meeting notes, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Mercenaries, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Micro array, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - Military funding, 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 73)
    - MIT, 1999-2004 (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - Monoclonal antibodies, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 75)
    - Monsanto, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 76)
    - Nanotechnology, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Neglected research, 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Negative results, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - Nelion, Dick, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - Neurontin, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 81)
    - Nexium, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 82)
    - NIH, 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 83)
    - North Carolina, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 84)
    - Novartis, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 85)
    - Nuremberg code, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 86)
    - Off lapel prescription, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 87)
    - OHRP, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 88)
    - Olivieri, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 89)
    - Onco mouse, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 90)
    - Open access, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 91)
    - Openness, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 92)
    - ORI, 2004-2006 (Box 15, Folder 93)
    - Patents- life forms, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Patents- innovation, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Personal accounts of experience in labs, 0003 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Patent payoffs, 2003-2005 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Peer review, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Pharmaceuticals, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Pharmaceutical industry criticism, 2000-2005 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Pharmaceutical lobbying, 2003-2005 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh, University of, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Pharmaceuticals- new drugs, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Pharmaceutical industry stats, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Post-docs and grad students, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Professional societies ethics role, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Public CIT, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Public vs. private value, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Public understanding, UK government advice to media, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Public trust, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Publication regulations, 2001-2003 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Publication restrictions by industry, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Publications competition, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Purity in contracting, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Research and development money, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Reach-through rights material transfer, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Regulations, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Research parks, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Research vs. teaching, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Restrictions on research, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Revolving door, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - RWJ meeting, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Rochester, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Rose, Hilary and Steve, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Salaries, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - San Diego, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Science commons, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Secrecy, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Serendipity, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Sports- university, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - State Tech training program, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Stats, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Statins, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Stem cells, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Stock market, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Swindlers, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Taxol, 2003-2005 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Tech training, 1997-2004 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Tissue ownership, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Tobacco, 2003-2005 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Tuition, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Tuskegee, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - UK, 2000-2003 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Universities- budgets, tuition, state cuts, growth, goals, 2000-2006 (Box 16, Folder 51-52)
    - Varmus, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Venter, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Venture capital, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Vioxx- celebrex, 2000-2005 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Wall street and science, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Wealthy academics, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Whitehead initiative, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - WHO- essential drugs, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Yale, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 61)
- Series III: University Information for "Science for Sale"
  - University of Michigan folders, reports, and notes, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - University of Pennsylvania interview texts, Gelsinger, folders, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 3-5)
  - Interview notes- Drummond Rennie, 2000-2006 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Interview texts- OHRP, AAHRPP, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Interview texts- NIH, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Interview texts- Columbia University, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Interview texts- University of Wisconsin, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Interview notes- McGill, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Correctives, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Interview texts- SLU, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Interview texts- Georgia Tech, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Interview texts- Washington University, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Interview texts, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Interview texts- University of Michigan, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Interview texts- MIT, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Conflict of interest, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - UCSF, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - AUTM report, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Ann Arbor, Madison, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Columbia visit, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Florida, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - AUTM, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - NIH- consulting, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - United Kingdom, 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - NIH ethics and surveys, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Interview texts- Florida State, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Interview texts- Stanford, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Interview texts- Koski, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - AEI-Brookings Joint Center symposium, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Patents, disclosures, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - IFAS paper, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Georgia Tech, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous pamphlets (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Series IV: Science and Technology Statistics
  - Science and Engineering Indicators reports, various published reports, 1976-2006 (Box 19-20)
- Series V: Scientific Misconduct
  - Articles and pamphlets, 1988-1994 (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
  - 20th Century fraud, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Borer decision, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Conference paper, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Workshop handbooks and reports, 1988-1994 (Box 21, Folder 8-11)
  - Miscellaneous notes and publications, 1987-1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Wilmhurst, 1978-1988 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Wilmhurst, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Erickson, 1983-1990 (Box 22, Folder 2-7)
- Series VI: Office of Technology Assessment
  - Miscellaneous articles and pamphlets, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 8-12)
  - NAE election, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - NAE- Liebowitz, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Issues of The Chronicle of Higher Education, 1996-2011 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Series VII: Science and Government Report
  - Science and Government Report - all issues, 1971-2007 (Box 24)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Books - cataloged individually in the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections
Science and Government Report International Almanac, Daniel Greenberg, editor. 1977
Science and Government Report International Almanac, Daniel Greenberg, editor. 1978-1979